Within the spreading darkness
I pledged a vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
I'm going to change
The future that
the forbidden fruit foretells...
I'm going to change
The dream into reality
The ending
That everybody wants
Within the spreading darkness
I pledged our vow to the revolution
I can't let anybody interrupt it
Someday I'll show you
A bright and ideal
World
SHINIGAMI REALM
What?
Two death's heads again?
Hah! I win.
Don't hold it against me.
Hey Ryuk... Do you wanna join us?
Join us, for once.
No, I'm okay.
I didn't do anything
but he still got upset...
Really? And then?
What's the matter, Yagami?
Please translate the sentence.
Follow the teachings of God.
Then the blessings of the sea
will become bountiful...
And there will be no storms.
Today, at approximately 11 a.m. in
Kanagawa Prefecture in Yokohama,
the body of a man appearing
to be about 30 years old
was found in an apartment,
covered in blood.
Kanagawa Police have opened
a homicide investigation.
In other news...
Today, shortly after noon,
Naoki Kofuji, 35, was arrested
in connection with the murder of
a 25-year-old female
he was living with
in the Shibuya district
of Tokyo.
Day in and day out. - -
the same thing 0 var and 0 var again.
Jeez. .. It's so ridiculous...
This world...
...is rotten.
REBIRTH
No way! You went to see that?
It was such a waste of time.
I shoulda' asked for a refund!
Well, you did watch it...
Death Note... Directly translated,
a notebook of death...
How to use it...
The human whose name is written
in this note...
shall die?
So stupid...
This is so sick.
lfis no cfifferenz'
from a chain letter.
"The human whose name is written
in this note shall die. . . "? C 'mon.
Seriously. . .
s0mething's the matter with me.
This note will not take effect
unless the writer
has the person's face in their mind
when writing his/her name. Therefore...
People sharing
the same name will not be affected.
If the cause of death is written
within 40 human seconds
of writing the person's name,
it will happen.
If the cause of death
is not specified,
the person will simply die
of a heart attack.
After writing the cause of death,
details of the death
should be written
in the next 6 minutes
and 40 seconds.
So you can let people die
peacefully or make them suffer.
A prank this intricate
isn't too bad, I guess.
Write in their name and they die, huh...
This is so stupid!
Wait a minute...
If someone actually dies,
does that make me a murderer?
No way. That's impossible.
The assailant who killed
six people yesterday...
at a busy shopping district
in Shinjuku...
has now taken
eight people hostage,
including children and teachers,
in this daycare center.
The police have now identified
the suspect
as 42-year-old Kurou Otoharada,
unemployed.
The police will begin negotiations
with the suspect.
KUROU OTOHARADA
A hean' attack in
forty seconds. - - night?
Well, that is not clear
at the moment.
You can't help but be worried
for the hostages right now.
Absolutely.
This has been a report
from the scene.
Thank you very much.
What do you think, Mr. Hashimoto?
Well, I'm hoping for
a quick resolution to this.
Oh well, nothing happened.
What did I expect?
Just a minute...
There seems to be
something happening.
The hostages are coming out!
They all seem to be all right!
And now it looks like
the SWAT team is entering!
Has the suspect been arrested?!
Yes!
We just received word
that the suspect has died
inside the daycare center!
The suspect is dead!
Dead?!
KUROU OTOHARADA
The police are strongly denying
that they shot the suspect!
Could he have felt cornered...
and committed suicide?
According to one of the hostages,
"the suspect suddenly collapsed. "
A heart attack...
N-No way...
This is a coincidence.
It's gotta be coincidence!
Light!
It's almost 6:30. Don't you have
your prep course tonight?
Yeah, I'm getting ready now.
Death Note...
But if this really works...
It's worth testing it out once more.
So I guess it will have
to be another criminal.
But it can't be someone
too famous.
If he dies, it's possible news
of it will be covered up.
I need an immediate result.
Hey, Ryo baby!
W-What is it, Sudou?
Lend me some money...
2000 yen will do.
W-What? Again?
Sudou...
- Shall I kill him?
- What'? You refusmg'?
No, I'd better avoid
people around me.
No... Why should I worry?
No one would care if one or
two people like him died.
Now we can go to
the arcade after school.
Maki, wanna party with
some guys tomorrow?
Absolutely!
Hey, me too!
Damn it, Mom!
She's not here to pick me up!
Damn it... It's sickening.
Every single one of them...
I'd do society a favor
by killing them.
Hey girl!
Wanna come and play with us?
Hey Taku!
You've got a beauty there!
I'm Takuo Shibuimaru.
Shibutaku, for short.
C'mon and join me...pretty girl.
I don't think so.
She doesn't think so!
She's so cute!
C'mon, grab her...
get those clothes off!
You sure?
S-Stop. . .!
Please!
Stop!
TAKUO SHIBUIMARU
ACCIDENTAL DEATH
Now let's see...
What'll happen!
Hey wait!
Taku! Watch out!
This... This proves it!
The Death Note is real!
Taku!
L-Idiot!
He just jumped out in front of me.
Now then...
I'd better get going.
It's been five days...since...
All right...
I'd better get going...
Huh? You going out, Ryuk?
This place is barren...
everywhere you go.
I dropped my Death Note.
You really messed up big time!
Hey, weren't you carrying around
a second one behind the old man's back?
You saying you lost both?
And do you know
where you dropped it?
The Human World.
- What?!
- What?
Welcome home.
You're early, Light.
Yeah.
I'm back, Mom.
Oh... The results of the national
practice entrance exams?
Hurry!
Here.
Goodness! Number one again!
You really did your best, Light!
Well yeah.
I'll be studying,
so don't interrupt me.
All right.
Oh Light...
Do you want anything?
Anything at all?
Not really, Mom.
I already have what I want...
You seem to like it.
Why so shocked?
I'm Ryuk, the Shinigami,
who dropped that notebook.
From what I just saw...
You're already aware that
it's no ordinary notebook.
A Shinigami...huh.
I'm not shocked, Ryuk.
In fact...
I've been waiting for you, Ryuk.
Oh?
I didn't think
a Shinigami's Notebook was real...
but after seeing its results,
I can act with certainty.
I see.
You've really surprised me...
I've heard of Death Notes getting down
to the Human World a few times before.
But you're the first one to use it
to this extent in just five days.
Most people would be
too scared to try it out.
I'm prepared, Ryuk.
I used the Death Note knowing
it belonged to a Shinigami.
And now the Shinigami's here.
So what'll happen to me?
Are you going to take my soul?
Huh? What's that about?
Is it some fantasy you humans
came up with?
I'm not going to do
anything to you.
Once the Death Note lands
in the Human World,
it belongs to the Human World.
In other words, that belongs to you.
It belongs to. . .me?
If you don't want it,
give it to some other human.
But if you do that,
all memory of the Death Note
will be erased from your mind.
So there isn't a price
for using the Death Note?
Well, if anything,
there's...
only the fear and pain humans who have
used the Death Note will experience.
And when you die...
I'll be the one to write
your name on my Death Note.
Don't think for a moment,
that any human...
who's used the Death Note
can go to Heaven or Hell.
That's all.
You'll find out about it
after you die.
Light...
Don't worry.
Go ahead.
What?
I brought some apples,
they're from our neighbor.
Why is it so dark in here?
You'll ruin your eyesight!
What's going on?
Mom can't see him?
That notebook...
originally belonged to me.
And since you're the one using it,
you're the only one who can see me...
and of course, only you...
Can hear my voice.
In other words,
the Death Note is a bond
between Light the human
and Ryuk the Shinigami.
Tasty.
Let me ask you one more thing.
Why did you choose me?
Hey, are you listening?
Hmm...apples in the
Human World are awesome.
What would you call them? Juicy?
Answer my question.
I didn't choose you.
I just dropped the notebook.
Did you think you were "chosen"
because you were smart?
Don't flatter yourself.
It just happened to fall around here...
and you just happened to pick it up.
That's all.
That's why I wrote the explanation
in English,
the most popular language
in the Human World.
Then why did you drop it?!
Don't tell me it was by mistake
after you went to the trouble and
wrote all those instructions.
Why'd I drop it?
...because I was bored.
Bored?
In fact, Shinigami these days
have so much time on their hands.
They're either taking a nap
or gambling.
If others see you studiously
scribbling names in the Death Note,
they'll say, "what are you working
so hard for?" and laugh at you.
Writing the names of other Shinigami
doesn't work.
But since we live
in the Shinigami Realm,
it's no fun at all to kill people
who live in the Human World!
So I figured it would be more fun
to come down here myself.
But you sure wrote a lotta names.
But Why'd you write down
the cause of death
only for that guy who
was hit by the truck?
Without the cause of
death written down,
they all die of heart attacks.
That's the best thing about
the Death Note, Ryuk.
I can write down
the names of the criminals...
and slowly reduce
the number of evil people.
What's the point?
Any fool can figure it out if someone
is just "eliminating the bad guys."
I want the world to know...
of my existence!
And that there's someone
who is passing judgment onto them!
But...what's the point
in passing judgment?
Why do it?
I was bored. . .too.
Naturally, I didn't believe it at first.
But that Death Note has
the supernatural power...
to tempt people to want
to try it at least once.
I-I killed them...
Two men- - - I killed them!
Human lives. . .
shouldn't be taken so lightly!
Do I have the right to
judge people like that?
No...
I'm not wrong!
I always thought about this...
The world is rotten!
And that rotten people
should die!
Someone...
Someone must do it!
Even if it means sacrificing
one's conscience and life!
Things can't stay. . .like this!
Even if someone else had
picked up the Death Note...
would they be able to erase
unwanted people from this world?
No way!
But I can... I can do it!
In fact, I'm the only one
who can do it!
And I will. ..
with the Death Note!
I'll change the world!
At first, I kept writing the names
of criminals...
like I was cleaning up the world.
So that in time,
no one would do evil.
While those guilty ones who truly
deserved to be punished for their crimes,
die of heart attacks...
people who were immoral
or harass others
will slowly be erased through
illness or accidents.
Then the world would truly
move in the right direction.
And I would create a new world of
earnest, kind humans.
Then you'd be the only one left. ..
with a bad personality.
Huh? What're you saying?
Ryuk...
I'm probably the best,
most diligent honor student in Japan.
And I...
will become the god
of this new world!
Humans...
are interesting, after all.
TO BE CONTINUED
I dreamed a dream
that no one could see
I threw away everything
that I didn't need
I'm holding these feelings
That I can't give up in my heart
Even if my feet fall victim
to the shackles of sacrifice
In between reality and my ideal
I can't hold back
the flooding impulses
Because I have a strong desire
To accomplish
[deceit] [fear] [vanity] [melancholy]
I'm not weak enough to believe
Any of these negative perceptions
I'm a trickster
who doesn't know solitude
PREVIEW
KIRA, KILL EVERYONE.
SEND MESSAGE?
SEND
The entire world is watching...
to see what happens
if anyone defies me. . .L.
NEXT EPISODE: CONFRONTATION